<?xml version="1.0"?>
<quiz>
<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/mix-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>Your company’s Azure subscription includes two Azure networks named VirtualNetworkA and VirtualNetworkB. VirtualNetworkA includes a VPN gateway that is configured to make use of static routing. Also, a site-to-site VPN connection exists between your company’s on-premises network and VirtualNetworkA. You have configured a point-to-site VPN connection to VirtualNetworkA from a workstation running Windows 10. After configuring virtual network peering between VirtualNetworkA and VirtualNetworkB, you confirm that you are able to access VirtualNetworkB from the company’s on-premises network. However, you find that you cannot establish a connection to VirtualNetworkB from the Windows 10 workstation. You have to make sure that a connection to VirtualNetworkB can be established from the Windows 10 workstation. Solution: You choose the Allow gateway transit setting on VirtualNetworkB. Does the solution meet the goal?</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Reference:</strong></h5><p>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/vpn-gateway/vpn-gateway-about-point-to-site-routing</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[<br/>Your company’s Azure subscription includes two Azure networks named VirtualNetworkA and VirtualNetworkB.<br/>VirtualNetworkA includes a VPN gateway that is configured to make use of static routing. Also, a site-to-site VPN connection exists between your company’s on-premises network and VirtualNetworkA.<br/><br/>You have configured a point-to-site VPN connection to VirtualNetworkA from a workstation running Windows 10. After configuring virtual network peering between VirtualNetworkA and VirtualNetworkB, you confirm that you are able to access VirtualNetworkB from the company’s on-premises network. However, you find that you cannot establish a connection to VirtualNetworkB from the Windows 10 workstation.<br/>You have to make sure that a connection to VirtualNetworkB can be established from the Windows 10 workstation.<br/><br/>Solution: You choose the Allow gateway transit setting on VirtualNetworkB. Does the solution meet the goal?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Yes</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>No</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/mix-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>Your company’s Azure subscription includes two Azure networks named VirtualNetworkA and VirtualNetworkB. VirtualNetworkA includes a VPN gateway that is configured to make use of static routing. Also, a site-to-site VPN connection exists between your company’s on-premises network and VirtualNetworkA. You have configured a point-to-site VPN connection to VirtualNetworkA from a workstation running Windows 10. After configuring virtual network peering between VirtualNetworkA and VirtualNetworkB, you confirm that you are able to access VirtualNetworkB from the company’s on-premises network. However, you find that you cannot establish a connection to VirtualNetworkB from the Windows 10 workstation. You have to make sure that a connection to VirtualNetworkB can be established from the Windows 10 workstation. Solution: You download and re-install the VPN client configuration package on the Windows 10 workstation. Does the solution meet the goal?</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Reference:</strong></h5><p>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/vpn-gateway/vpn-gateway-about-point-to-site-routing</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[<br/>Your company’s Azure subscription includes two Azure networks named VirtualNetworkA and VirtualNetworkB.<br/>VirtualNetworkA includes a VPN gateway that is configured to make use of static routing. Also, a site-to-site VPN connection exists between your company’s on-premises network and VirtualNetworkA.<br/><br/>You have configured a point-to-site VPN connection to VirtualNetworkA from a workstation running Windows 10. After configuring virtual network peering between VirtualNetworkA and VirtualNetworkB, you confirm that you are able to access VirtualNetworkB from the company’s on-premises network. However, you find that you cannot establish a connection to VirtualNetworkB from the Windows 10 workstation.<br/>You have to make sure that a connection to VirtualNetworkB can be established from the Windows 10 workstation.<br/><br/>Solution: You download and re-install the VPN client configuration package on the Windows 10 workstation. Does the solution meet the goal?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>Yes</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>No</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/mix-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>Your company has virtual machines (VMs) hosted in Microsoft Azure. The VMs are located in a single Azure virtual network named VNet1. The company has users that work remotely. The remote workers require access to the VMs on VNet1. You need to provide access for the remote workers. What should you do?</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Explanation:</strong></h5><p>A Point-to-Site (P2S) VPN gateway connection lets you create a secure connection to your virtual network from an individual client computer.</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[Your company has virtual machines (VMs) hosted in Microsoft Azure. The VMs are located in a single Azure virtual network named VNet1.<br/>The company has users that work remotely. The remote workers require access to the VMs on VNet1. You need to provide access for the remote workers.<br/>What should you do?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Configure a Site-to-Site (S2S) VPN.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Configure a VNet-toVNet VPN.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>Configure a Point-to-Site (P2S) VPN.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Configure DirectAccess on a Windows Server 2012 server VM.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Configure a Multi-Site VPN</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/mix-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>Your company has a Microsoft SQL Server Always On availability group configured on their Azure virtual machines (VMs). You need to configure an Azure internal load balancer as a listener for the availability group. Solution: You create an HTTP health probe on port 1433. Does the solution meet the goal?</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[<br/>Your company has a Microsoft SQL Server Always On availability group configured on their Azure virtual machines (VMs).<br/>You need to configure an Azure internal load balancer as a listener for the availability group.<br/><br/>Solution: You create an HTTP health probe on port 1433.<br/>Does the solution meet the goal?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Yes</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>No</text>
</answer>
</question>

</quiz>
