<?xml version="1.0"?>
<quiz>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>Your company has an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) subscription. You need to deploy five virtual machines (VMs) to your company’s virtual network subnet. The VMs will each have both a public and private IP address. Inbound and outbound security rules for all of these virtual machines must be identical. Which of the following is the least amount of security groups needed for this configuration?</text></name>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[Your company has an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) subscription.<br/>You need to deploy five virtual machines (VMs) to your company’s virtual network subnet.<br/>The VMs will each have both a public and private IP address. Inbound and outbound security rules for all of these virtual machines must be identical.<br/>Which of the following is the least amount of security groups needed for this configuration?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>4</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>3</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>2</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>1</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>Your company’s Azure subscription includes Azure virtual machines (VMs) that run Windows Server 2016. One of the VMs is backed up every day using Azure Backup Instant Restore. When the VM becomes infected with data encrypting ransomware, you decide to recover the VM’s files.  Which of the following is TRUE in this scenario?</text></name>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[Your company’s Azure subscription includes Azure virtual machines (VMs) that run Windows Server 2016. One of the VMs is backed up every day using Azure Backup Instant Restore.<br/>When the VM becomes infected with data encrypting ransomware, you decide to recover the VM’s files. <br/>Which of the following is TRUE in this scenario?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>You can only recover the files to the infected VM.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>You can recover the files to any VM within the company’s subscription.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>You can only recover the files to a new VM.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>You will not be able to recover the files.</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>Your company’s Azure subscription includes Azure virtual machines (VMs) that run Windows Server 2016. One of the VMs is backed up every day using Azure Backup Instant Restore. When the VM becomes infected with data encrypting ransomware, you are required to restore the VM.  Which of the following actions should you take?</text></name>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[Your company’s Azure subscription includes Azure virtual machines (VMs) that run Windows Server 2016. One of the VMs is backed up every day using Azure Backup Instant Restore.<br/>When the VM becomes infected with data encrypting ransomware, you are required to restore the VM. <br/>Which of the following actions should you take?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>You should restore the VM after deleting the infected VM.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>You should restore the VM to any VM within the company’s subscription.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>You should restore the VM to a new Azure VM.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>You should restore the VM to an on-premise Windows device.</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>You administer a solution in Azure that is currently having performance issues. You need to find the cause of the performance issues pertaining to metrics on the Azure infrastructure.  Which of the following is the tool you should use?</text></name>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[You administer a solution in Azure that is currently having performance issues.<br/>You need to find the cause of the performance issues pertaining to metrics on the Azure infrastructure. <br/>Which of the following is the tool you should use?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Azure Traffic Analytics</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>Azure Monitor</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Azure Activity Log</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Azure Advisor</text>
</answer>
</question>

</quiz>
