<?xml version="1.0"?>
<quiz>
<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/manage-azure-identities-and-governance-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>You have an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) tenant named contosocloud.onmicrosoft.com. Your company has a public DNS zone for contoso.com. You add contoso.com as a custom domain name to Azure AD. You need to ensure that Azure can verify the domain name. Which type of DNS record should you create?</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Reference:</strong></h5><p>https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/dns/dns-web-sites-custom-domain</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[You have an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) tenant named contosocloud.onmicrosoft.com. Your company has a public DNS zone for contoso.com.<br/>You add contoso.com as a custom domain name to Azure AD. You need to ensure that Azure can verify the domain name. <br/>Which type of DNS record should you create?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>MX</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>NSEC</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>SRV</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>NSEC3</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/manage-azure-identities-and-governance-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>You have an Azure Directory (Azure AD) tenant named Adatum and an Azure Subscription named Subscription1. Adatum contains a group named Developers. Subscription1 contains a resource group named Dev. You need to provide the Developers group with the ability to create Azure logic apps in the Dev resource group. Solution: On Subscription1, you assign the DevTest Labs User role to the Developers group. Does this meet the goal?</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Explanation:</strong></h5><p>DevTest Labs User role only lets you connect, start, restart, and shutdown virtual machines in your Azure DevTest Labs.<br/>The Logic App Contributor role lets you manage logic app, but not access to them. It provides access to view, edit, and update a logic app.</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[<br/><br/><br/>You have an Azure Directory (Azure AD) tenant named Adatum and an Azure Subscription named Subscription1. Adatum contains a group named Developers. Subscription1 contains a resource group named Dev.<br/><br/>You need to provide the Developers group with the ability to create Azure logic apps in the Dev resource group.<br/><br/>Solution: On Subscription1, you assign the DevTest Labs User role to the Developers group.<br/>Does this meet the goal?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Yes</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>No</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/manage-azure-identities-and-governance-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>You have an Azure Directory (Azure AD) tenant named Adatum and an Azure Subscription named Subscription1. Adatum contains a group named Developers. Subscription1 contains a resource group named Dev. You need to provide the Developers group with the ability to create Azure logic apps in the Dev resource group. Solution: On Subscription1, you assign the Logic App Operator role to the Developers group. Does this meet the goal?</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Explanation:</strong></h5><p>You would need the Logic App Contributor role.</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[<br/><br/><br/>You have an Azure Directory (Azure AD) tenant named Adatum and an Azure Subscription named Subscription1. Adatum contains a group named Developers. Subscription1 contains a resource group named Dev.<br/><br/>You need to provide the Developers group with the ability to create Azure logic apps in the Dev resource group.<br/><br/>Solution: On Subscription1, you assign the Logic App Operator role to the Developers group.<br/>Does this meet the goal?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Yes</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>No</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/manage-azure-identities-and-governance-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>You have an Azure Directory (Azure AD) tenant named Adatum and an Azure Subscription named Subscription1. Adatum contains a group named Developers. Subscription1 contains a resource group named Dev. You need to provide the Developers group with the ability to create Azure logic apps in the Dev resource group. Solution: On Dev, you assign the Contributor role to the Developers group. Does this meet the goal?</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Explanation:</strong></h5><p>The Contributor role can manage all resources (and add resources) in a Resource Group.</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[<br/><br/><br/>You have an Azure Directory (Azure AD) tenant named Adatum and an Azure Subscription named Subscription1. Adatum contains a group named Developers. Subscription1 contains a resource group named Dev.<br/><br/>You need to provide the Developers group with the ability to create Azure logic apps in the Dev resource group.<br/><br/>Solution: On Dev, you assign the Contributor role to the Developers group.<br/>Does this meet the goal?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>Yes</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>No</text>
</answer>
</question>

</quiz>
