<?xml version="1.0"?>
<quiz>
<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/manage-azure-identities-and-governance-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>You have an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) tenant named contoso.onmicrosoft.com. The User administrator role is assigned to a user named Admin1. An external partner has a Microsoft account that uses the user1@outlook.com sign in. Admin1 attempts to invite the external partner to sign in to the Azure AD tenant and receives the following error message: “Unable to invite user user1@outlook.com – Generic authorization exception.” You need to ensure that Admin1 can invite the external partner to sign in to the Azure AD tenant. What should you do?</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Reference:</strong></h5><p>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/Azure-Active-Directory/Generic-authorization-exception-inviting-Azure-AD-gests/td-p/274742</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[You have an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) tenant named contoso.onmicrosoft.com. The User administrator role is assigned to a user named Admin1.<br/>An external partner has a Microsoft account that uses the user1@outlook.com sign in.<br/><br/>Admin1 attempts to invite the external partner to sign in to the Azure AD tenant and receives the following error message: “Unable to invite user user1@outlook.com – Generic authorization exception.”<br/><br/>You need to ensure that Admin1 can invite the external partner to sign in to the Azure AD tenant. <br/>What should you do?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>From the Users blade, modify the External collaboration settings.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>From the Custom domain names blade, add a custom domain.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>From the Organizational relationships blade, add an identity provider.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>From the Roles and administrators blade, assign the Security administrator role to Admin1.</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/manage-azure-identities-and-governance-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>You have an Azure subscription that contains a user account named User1. You need to ensure that User1 can assign a policy to the tenant root management group. What should you do?</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Explanation:</strong></h5><p>The following chart shows the list of roles and the supported actions on management groups.<br/><img id="img80" src="https://free-braindumps.com/images/exam-dumps/AZ-104/efde83fe-13e9-4991-983e-fb2f77af095c.jpg" imageviewer=""/><br/><br/>Note:<br/>Each directory is given a single top-level management group called the &#34;Root&#34; management group. This root management group is built into the hierarchy to have all management groups and subscriptions fold up to it. This root management group allows for global policies and Azure role assignments to be applied at the directory level. The Azure AD Global Administrator needs to elevate themselves to the User Access Administrator role of this root group initially. After elevating access, the administrator can assign any Azure role to other directory users or groups to manage the hierarchy. As administrator, you can assign your own account as owner of the root management group.</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[You have an Azure subscription that contains a user account named User1.<br/>You need to ensure that User1 can assign a policy to the tenant root management group. <br/>What should you do?]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Assign the Owner role for the Azure Subscription to User1, and then modify the default conditional access policies.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>Assign the Owner role for the Azure subscription to User1, and then instruct User1 to configure access management for Azure resources.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Assign the Global administrator role to User1, and then instruct User1 to configure access management for Azure resources.</text>
</answer>
<answer fraction="0">
<text>Create a new management group and delegate User1 as the owner of the new management group.</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/manage-azure-identities-and-governance-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>HOTSPOT (Drag and Drop is not supported) You have an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) tenant named adatum.com. Adatum.com contains the groups in the following table.   You create two user accounts that are configured as shown in the following table.  To which groups do User1 and User2 belong? To answer, select the appropriate options in the answer area. Hot Area:</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Explanation:</strong></h5><p><img id="img88" src="https://free-braindumps.com/images/exam-dumps/AZ-104/3849104b-0823-416d-9420-a36075abe6a8.jpg" imageviewer=""/><br/><br/><br/>Box 1: Group 1 only First rule applies<br/>Box 2: Group1 and Group2 only Both membership rules apply.</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[HOTSPOT (Drag and Drop is not supported)<br/>You have an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) tenant named adatum.com. Adatum.com contains the groups in the following table.<br/><br/><img id="img82" src="https://free-braindumps.com/images/exam-dumps/AZ-104/711537d4-1e93-4adf-b31b-c5abad2385b2.jpg" imageviewer=""/><br/><br/>You create two user accounts that are configured as shown in the following table.<br/><img id="img84" src="https://free-braindumps.com/images/exam-dumps/AZ-104/80cd6e7f-711f-45f1-9c0e-53f2bef5eeb2.jpg" imageviewer=""/><br/><br/>To which groups do User1 and User2 belong? To answer, select the appropriate options in the answer area.<br/><br/>Hot Area:<br/><br/><img id="img86" src="https://free-braindumps.com/images/exam-dumps/AZ-104/fe598cb9-caf2-40c9-b9ea-69fc0d31e9ec.jpg" imageviewer=""/>]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>See Explanation section for answer.</text>
</answer>
</question>

<question type="category">
<category><text>$course$/manage-azure-identities-and-governance-questions</text></category>
</question>
<question type="multichoice">
<name><text>HOTSPOT (Drag and Drop is not supported) You have a hybrid deployment of Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) that contains the users shown in the following table.   You need to modify the JobTitle and UsageLocation attributes for the users. For which users can you modify the attributes from Azure AD? To answer, select the appropriate options in the answer area. Hot Area:</text></name>
<generalfeedback format="html"><text><![CDATA[<h5><strong>Explanation:</strong></h5><p><img id="img94" src="https://free-braindumps.com/images/exam-dumps/AZ-104/47e7a08f-6c7e-4d95-91b1-c75e0b36112a.jpg" imageviewer=""/><br/><br/><br/>Box 1: User1 and User3 only<br/><br/>You must use Windows Server Active Directory to update the identity, contact info, or job info for users whose source of authority is Windows Server Active Directory.<br/>Box 2: User1, User2, and User3</p>]]></text></generalfeedback>
<questiontext format="html"><text><![CDATA[HOTSPOT (Drag and Drop is not supported)<br/>You have a hybrid deployment of Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) that contains the users shown in the following table.<br/><br/><img id="img90" src="https://free-braindumps.com/images/exam-dumps/AZ-104/c8b2b09e-2b69-4638-bc4d-484c0dc5b6b8.jpg" imageviewer=""/><br/><br/>You need to modify the JobTitle and UsageLocation attributes for the users.<br/><br/>For which users can you modify the attributes from Azure AD? To answer, select the appropriate options in the answer area.<br/><br/>Hot Area:<br/><br/><img id="img92" src="https://free-braindumps.com/images/exam-dumps/AZ-104/46e4d62d-e22d-4442-a5aa-8ca4926b22db.jpg" imageviewer=""/>]]></text></questiontext>
<answernumbering>abc</answernumbering>
<answer fraction="100">
<text>See Explanation section for answer.</text>
</answer>
</question>

</quiz>
